# Deepika Lalge () Featured

SME in Oracle WebCenter Content - Troubleshooting Support issues + Development Tasks + Portal Development and Integration between Portal and WCM. Worked on Oracle UCM ,IPM, Capture Workspace, URM, IRM and its configuration and integrations.



Current Designation: Associate Analyst Total Experience: 8 Year(s) 0 Month(s)

Current Company: Eaton Technologies Private Limited Notice Period: 2 Months

Current Location: Pune Highest Degree: MCA [Computers]

Pref. Location: Pune

Functional Area: IT Software - Application Programming /

Maintenance

Role: Software Developer

Industry: IT-Software/Software Services

Marital Status: Married

Key Skills: Oracle Fusion Middleware(Webcenter Content UCM, Oracle Imaging, URM, IRM, Oracle WebCenter Capture,

Portal Development, Bmc Remedy

Verified: Phone Number | Email - id

Last Active: 18-Jan-21 Last Modified: 18-Jan-21

## Summary

Having around 8 Years of experience in the IT Industry

Hands on experience on Oracle WebCenter Content 11g

Experienced in developing applications using IDEs like JDeveloper

Experience on Versioning Tool Subversion using JDeveloper.

Experience on Installation of and configuration of Oracle WebCenter Content product.

Overall Configuration of UCM profiles, IPM applications, capture workspace, IRM and configuration, Workflow configuration between UCM-BPM/BPEL

# **Work Experience**

# Eaton Technologies Private Limited as Associate Analyst

Dec 2015 to Till Date

Support and Development Responsibilities:

- \* Currently working on Content Management and Portal Support related Tickets which includes access, channels, applications, LDAP related and Content addition/modification/updates
- \* Handled Ticket with different such as account lock, channel and application access, data correction, passkey, supplier-customer user type issues and Portal and WCM configuration.
- \* Built Strong relationship with the online/offline customer via IM/mails/calls for clear understanding.
- \* Visited client location to face the client with their issues instantly to support them with all their queries and issues requested.
- \* Keeping always in touch with customers for the better business and support.
- \* Responding them on priority on any technical issues raised on urgency.
- \* Took over all responsible related to any Content Management related issues and accordingly prepared troubleshooting documents for future use.
- \* Worked on Incidents and Requests Tickets within the SLA Breach.
- \* Worked with customers on urgency basis in a proactive manner for the issues assigned.
- \* Worked on various types of Development Work Items/Jira Stories.
- Documented on newer issues raised for future purpose.
- \* Worked on UI changes (CSS) kind of WI's
- Worked on one Bench Work Item for performance issues on all admin and managed servers.

- \* Contributed time for contractors in providing KT along with daily task.
- Worked on 52312 Annual Certificate Renewal Project (SSO).

#### **TACME** as Software Engineer

Jul 2015 to Nov 2015

UAQ Project, Dubai.

Project Scope & Responsibilities:

- \* Application need to open the Scanner Page configured in the machine when employee selects the "Scan the Document"
- \* Employee will scan the page and application need to upload the document in the UCM Server and return the Content id and other required details.

Role: Application Developer

- \* Installation of and configuration of Oracle WebCenter Content product
- \* Installation of WebLogic Server.
- \* Installation of RCU for Schema.
- \* Installation of WebCenter Capture.
- \* Patch Application
- Configuration of Capture profile to commit to IPM application.
- Configuration of BPM workflow with the IPM application to trigger
- \* Enabled and configured integration between UCM- BPM workflow.
- \* Creation of IPM application and search profile.

#### KPIT Technologies Ltd as OFM Consultant

Oct 2012 to Jul 2015

Mannai-DMS Implementation of Web Center Content, Qatar

Project Scope & Responsibilities

Installation of and configuration of Oracle WebCenter Content product

Installation of WebLogic Server.

Installation of SOA.

Installation of RCU for Schema.

Installation of WebCenter Capture.

Patch Application

Configuration of Capture profile to commit to IPM application.

Configuration of BPM workflow with the IPM application to trigger the approval task.

Prepared System prerequisite checklist for installation of the software.

Configured LDAP provider with WebLogic console for user authentication.

Installed and Configured UCM Components.

Creation of IPM application and search profile

Migration of Capture profile from DEV to TEST instance.

Import and export of IPM application from DEV to TEST.

Creation of metadata field in UCM.

Creation of Roles/Groups.

Enabled and configured integration between UCM-BPM workflow.

Configuration credential map for the user role in UCM.

Installation of DIS.

Configuration of UCM workflow.

Configuration of IRM for sealing the content.

Configuration of URM for expiration of the content.

Configuration the Content Categorizer.

Complete System to system migration using CMU.

Creation of Setup document for installation and configuration for both DEV and TEST environment in the Project repository (SVN).

Involved in Document preparation.

### **Education**

UG: BCA (Computers) from Karnataka University in 2009

PG: MCA (Computers) from Visveswaraiah Technological University (VTU) in 2012

### IT Skills

Skill Name	Version	Last Used	Experience
Windows XP, Windows 7, Windows 8/8.1			
Linux			
Java, SQL			
Oracle Products			
Oracle WebLogic Application Server, UCM			
ORACLE 10G			
Subversion Navigator (SVN), Bitbucket			
ISSUETRACKER			
JDeveloper, Site Studio Designer			
MSSQL Server, and MS Access, Oracle SQL			

# Languages Known

Language	Proficiency	Read	Write	Speak
English	Expert			
Hindi	Expert			
Kannada	Expert			
Marathi	Expert			

### **Affirmative Action**

Category: General

Job Type: Permanent

Physically Challenged: No

Employment Status: Full time

**Work Authorization**